▍2026 美网 男单第二轮
勒纳·钱 6-3 6-4 6-3 孟菲尔斯 · 赛后告别仪式
G, you have given so much to this city,
你为这座城市付出了太多
these fans, this sport.
为这些球迷，为这项运动
We would love
我们很想听你说说
to hear how much it's all meant to you.
这一切对你意味着什么
Good evening, New York.
晚上好，纽约
I want to thank you all.
我想谢谢你们所有人
I mean, it's been a long ride.
这是很长的一段路
I came here in 2003 for the juniors
我2003年来这儿打青少年组
for the first time and here I am in 2026.
那是第一次，而现在是2026年
So, it's a had a long ride.
真的是很长的一段路
So, thank you very much.
所以，非常感谢
I felt all this year the love
这一年我一直感受着这份爱
and I can tell you you guys
我可以告诉你们
are my second best crowd of course
你们是我第二好的观众
after Paris but you're up there so thank you
当然，排在巴黎之后
so much.
太感谢了
I just want to just to tell you it's
我只想告诉你们
been a absolute honor for me
这对我是莫大的荣幸
to play all this year in front of you.
这些年能在你们面前打球
Try my best,
尽我所能
try to perform high performance tennis,
打出高水平的网球
but also give you a great show
同时也给你们一场好看的表演
and you guys give me great love.
而你们给了我巨大的爱
So, you know, I will never forget that.
我永远不会忘记
So, thank you very much for everything.
谢谢你们的一切
Thank you, Neil.
谢谢你
Well, Gael, now USTA CEO Craig Tiley and
美国网协CEO克雷格·泰利
US Open tournament director Eric Butorac
和美网赛事总监布托拉克
are going to present you with a special gift.
将为你送上一份特别的礼物
What a moment.
多么重要的时刻
For the final time here in New York,
在纽约的最后一次
let's hear it for Gael Monfils.
让我们为孟菲尔斯欢呼